19th-20th Century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 15)
    - Chicago, IL (Box 35)
      - Office Buildings (Box 40)
        - Continental Insurance (Box 40)
        - Daily News (Box 41)
        - Dexter (Box 41)
        - Dwight Building (Box 41)
        - Federal Center (Box 41)
        - Field (Box 41)
        - Gage Building (Box 41)
        - John Hancock Center (Box 41)
        - Hartford Insurance Building (Box 41)
        - Hennebery (Box 41)
        - Home Insurance Building (Box 41)
        - Inland Steel Building (Box 41)
        - Leiter Building (Box 41)
        - Manhattan Building (Box 41)
        - Marquette Building (Box 41)
        - McClurg Building (Box 41)
        - Meyer Building (Box 41)
        - Monadnock Building (Box 41)
        - Montauck Building (Box 41)
        - Nelson Building (Box 41)
        - Nepeenauk Building (Box 41)
        - Northeast Airlines (Box 41)
        - Old Colony Building (Box 41)
        - Palmolive (Box 41)
        - Railway Exchange (Box 41)
        - Rand McNally (Box 41)
        - Reliance Building (Box 41)
        - Republic Building (Box 41)
        - Rookery Building (Box 41)
        - Schiller Building (Box 41)
        - Schlessinger & Mayer Building (Box 41)
        - Selz, Schwab, Co (Box 41)
        - Studebaker Building (Box 41)
        - Tacoma Building (Box 41)
        - Tribune Building & Tribune Competition (Box 41)
        - Troescher Building (Box 41)
        - TWA Office (Box 42)
        - Willoughby Building (Box 42)
        - Wrigley (Box 42)
      - Parks (Box 42)
        - Aquarium (Box 42)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 42)
        - Great Central (Box 42)
        - Union Station (Box 42)
      - Restaurants (Box 42)
      - Schools (Box 42)
        - Various (Box 42)
        - Illinois Institute of Technology (Box 42)
          - Various (Box 42)
          - Chapel (Box 42)
          - Crown Hall (Box 42)
          - Memorial Hall (Box 42)
          - Metals Research Building (Box 42)
        - University of Chicago (Box 42)
      - Squares (Box 43)
      - Stadiums (Box 43)
      - Stores (Box 43)
        - Various (Box 43)
        - Carson-Pirie Scott Store (Box 43)
        - Fair Store (Box 43)
        - Marshall Field Store (Box 43)
          General
          Xx Warehouses
        - Schlesinger & Meyer Department Store (Box 43)
          Xx Carson-Pirie Scott
        - Straus & Schram Department Store (Box 43)
        - Edinson Serop (Box 43)
      - Theaters (Box 43)
        - Various (Box 43)
        - Civic Opera Building (Box 43)
      - Tombs (Box 43)
      - Warehouses (Box 43)
    - Chicopee, GA (Box 43)
    - Chimayo, NM (Box 43)
    - Chisholm House, SC (Box 43)
    - Cincinnati, OH (Box 43)
      - General (Box 43)
      - Bridges (Box 43)
      - Cemeteries (Box 43)
      - Churches (Box 43)
      - Houses (Box 43)
      - Government Buildings (Box 43)
      - Museums (Box 43)
    - Ciderville, OH (Box 44)
    - Ciudad Juarez, NM (Box 44)
    - Clemson, SC (Box 44)
    - Cleveland, OH (Box 44)
      - General Views (Box 44)
      - Airports (Box 44)
      - Churches (Box 44)
      - Houses (Box 44)
      - Housing (Box 44)
      - Industrial Building (Box 44)
      - Museums (Box 44)
        - Museum of Art (Box 44)
    - Clinton, IA (Box 44)
    - Clinton, LA (Box 44)
    - Clinton, NY (Box 44)
    - Cloquet, MN (Box 44)
      - Gas Station (Box 44)
      - Lindholm House (Box 44)
    - Cohasset, MA (Box 44)
    - Colchester, CT (Box 44)
    - Colebrook, CT (Box 44)
    - Collegeville, MN (Box 45)
    - Colorado Springs, CO (Box 45)
    - Columbia, SC (Box 45)
    - Columbia, TE (Box 45)
    - Columbus, ID (Box 45)
    - Columbus, OH (Box 45)
      - Government Buildings (Box 45)
    - Columbus, WI (Box 45)
      - Houses (Box 45)
    - Comondu, CA (Box 45)
    - Concord, NH (Box 45)
    - Concord, MA (Box 45)
      - Various (Box 45)
      - Wright Tavern (Box 45)
      - Houses (Box 45)
        - Old Manse (Box 45)
    - Conroe, TX (Box 45)
    - Constitution Island- Hundson River, NY (Box 45)
    - Convent, LA (Box 45)
    - Cooperstown, NY (Box 45)
    - Coral Gables, FL (Box 45)
    - Cornwall, CT (Box 45)
    - Corpus Christ, TX (Box 46)
    - Corydon, IN (Box 46)
    - Cottage Grove, OR (Box 46)
    - Council Bluffs, IA (Box 46)
    - Coventry, CT (Box 46)
    - Crab Orchard (Box 46)
    - Craftsman Farms, NJ (Box 46)
    - Cragfont, TN (Box 46)
    - Cronwell, CT (Box 46)
    - Croton-On-Hudson, NY (Box 46)
    - Croydon, PA (Box 46)
    - Crystal City, MO (Box 46)
    - Cuary, NM (Box 46)
    - Cumberland, RI (Box 46)
    - Dallas, TX (Box 46)
      - Banks (Box 46)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 46)
        - Marcus House (Box 46)
      - Stores (Box 46)
        - Nieman-Marcus Store (Box 46)
    - Danvers, MA (Box 46)
      - Houses (Box 46)
        - "The Linders" (Box 46)
        - Hooper-Collins House (Box 46)
    - Danville, KY (Box 46)
    - Darby, MT (Box 46)
    - Darien, CT (Box 46)
    - Darlington, WI (Box 46)
    - Dayton, OH (Box 46)
    - Dayton Beach, FL (Box 46)
    - Davenport, IA (Box 46)
    - Davidson College, NC (Box 46)
    - Deadwood City, SD (Box 47)
    - Dearborn, MI (Box 47)
    - Decatur, IL (Box 47)
    - Dedham, MA (Box 47)
    - Deepdale, L.I., NY (Box 47)
    - Deerfield, MA (Box 47)
    - Delanto Park, ME (Box 47)
    - Delevan Lake, WI (Box 47)
    - Delmar, CA (Box 47)
    - Demopolis, AL (Box 47)
    - Dennis, MA (Box 47)
    - Denver, CO (Box 47)
    - Des Moines, IA (Box 47)
      - Banks (Box 47)
      - Houses (Box 47)
      - Museums (Box 47)
      - Schools (Box 47)
    - Detroit, MI (Box 47)
      - General (Box 47–48)
      - Banks (Box 48)
      - Churches (Box 48)
      - Government Buildings (Box 48)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 48)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 48)
        - Various (Box 48)
        - Chalmers Motor Co. (Box 48)
        - Chrysler Halfton Truck Part (Box 48)
        - Ford Co. (Box 48)
        - General Motors Center (Box 48)
          - Exteriors (Box 48)
          - Interiors (Box 48)
        - Monell St. Power Plant (Box 48)
      - Libraries (Box 48)
      - Museums (Box 48)
        - Institute of Art (Box 48)
      - Office Buildings (Box 49)
        - American Concrete Institute Headquarters (Box 49)
        - Reynolds Metal Building (Box 49)
      - Schools (Box 49)
        - Society of Arts & Crafts (Box 49)
        - Wayne University (Box 49)
    - Dobbs Ferry, NY (Box 49)
    - Dolton, IL (Box 49)
    - Dorchester, MA (Box 49)
    - Dorchester Heights, MA (Box 49)
    - Doughregan Manor Howard Co, MO (Box 49)
    - Dover, NH (Box 49)
    - Downers Grove, IL (Box 49)
    - Durham, CT (Box 49)
    - Durham, NH (Box 49)
    - Duxbury, MA (Box 49)
    - East Brimfield, MA (Box 49)
    - East Granby, CT (Box 49)
    - East Haddam, CT (Box 49)
    - East Hampton, NH (Box 49)
    - East Hampton, NY (Box 49)
      - Houses (Box 49)
        - Various (Box 49)
        - Lanser House (Box 49)
    - East Hartford, CT (Box 50)
    - East Haven, C (Box 50)
    - East Lyme, CT (Box 50)
    - East Orange, NJ (Box 50)
      - Houses (Box 50)
    - East Sandwich, MA (Box 50)
    - East Windsor, CT (Box 50)
    - Eastwood, NY (Box 50)
    - Economy Ambridge (Box 50)
    - Edenton, NC (Box 50)
    - Eddington, PA (Box 50)
    - Edgewater, IL (Box 50)
    - Edisto, SC (Box 50)
    - Elberon, NJ (Box 50)
      - Houses (Box 50)
        - Cook House (Box 50)
        - Guggenheim House (Box 50)
        - Newcomb House (Box 50)
      - Recreation (Box 50)
    - El Cerrito, CA (Box 50)
    - Elicotteity, MD (Box 50)
    - Elkhart, IN (Box 50)
    - Elkins Park, PA (Box 50)
    - Ellerville, FL (Box 50)
    - Elmhurst, IL (Box 50)
    - El Paso, TX (Box 51)
    - Elsah, IL (Box 51)
    - Elys Landing, CT (Box 51)
    - Enfield, CT (Box 51)
    - Englewood, NJ (Box 51)
    - Ephrata, PA (Box 51)
    - Essex, CT (Box 51)
      Xx Architecture U.S. - Guilford, CT, Chamberlain House
    - Essex, MA (Box 51)
    - Eureka, CA (Box 51)
    - Evanston, IL (Box 51)
    - Fairfield, AL (Box 51)
    - Fairfield, CT (Box 51)
    - Fair Haven, CT (Box 51)
    - Fairhills, CA (Box 51)
    - Fall River, MA (Box 51)
    - Farmington, CT (Box 51)
      - Houses (Box 51)
        - George Solomon Cowles House (Box 51)
        - Samuel Cowles-Lewis House, 1782 (Box 51)
        - Timothy Cowles House (Box 51)
        - Whitman House (Box 52)
    - Far Rockaway, LI (Box 52)
    - Fisher's Island, NY (Box 52)
    - Fishkill, NY (Box 52)
    - Fitchburg, MA (Box 52)
    - Forest Hills Gardens, NY (Box 52)
    - Fort Jefferson, FL (Box 52)
    - Fort Knox (Box 52)
    - Fort Niagara (Box 52)
    - Fort Riley (Box 52)
    - Fort Ticonderoga (Box 52)
    - Fort Wayne, IN (Box 52)
    - Fort Worth, TX (Box 52)
    - Framingham, MA (Box 52)
    - Francisville, LA (Box 52)
    - Frankfort, KY (Box 52)
    - Frederica, GA (Box 52)
    - Fredericksburg, VA (Box 52)
      - Houses (Box 52)
        - Kenmore (Box 52)
    - Freetown, MA (Box 52)
    - Frenchtown, NJ (Box 52)
    - Fresno, CA (Box 53)
      - Government Buildings (Box 53)
        - City Hall (Box 53)
      - Schools (Box 53)
    - Galesburg, IL (Box 53)
    - Galveston (Box 53)
    - Gardena, CA (Box 53)
    - Gardiner, ME (Box 53)
    - Garrison-On-Hudson, NY (Box 53)
    - Geneseo, NY (Box 53)
    - Georgetown, DC (Box 53)
    - Georgetown, KY (Box 53)
    - Georgetown, SC (Box 53)
    - Georgia, VT (Box 53)
    - Germantown, PA (Box 53)
      Xx under Philadelphia
    - Geyerville, CA (Box 53)
    - Glencoe, IL (Box 53)
    - Glen Cove, L.I., NY (Box 53)
    - Glendale, CA (Box 53)
    - Glen Echo Heights, MD (Box 53)
    - Glen Ellyn, IL (Box 53)
    - Gloucester, MA (Box 53)
    - Good Hope, LA (Box 53)
    - Goose Creek, SC (Box 53)
    - Governor's Island, NY (Box 53)
    - Grand Beach, MI (Box 53)
    - Grand Meadow, MI (Box 53)
    - Grand Rapids, MI (Box 53)
    - Grand Quivira (Box 54)
    - Granite, MA (Box 54)
    - Grass Lake, ME (Box 54)
    - Great Lakes, IL (Box 54)
    - Great Neck, NY (Box 54)
    - Greenbelt, MD (Box 54)
    - Greendale, WI (Box 54)
    - Greendale on Hudson, NY (Box 54)
    - Greenfield, MA (Box 54)
    - Greensburg, PA (Box 54)
    - Greenville, SC (Box 54)
    - Greenwich, CT (Box 54)
      - Planning (Box 54)
      - Houses (Box 54)
    - Grinnell, IA (Box 54)
    - Grosse Pointe, MI (Box 54)
    - Guilford, CT (Box 54)
      - Various (Box 54)
      - Churches (Box 55)
      - Houses (Box 55)
        - Various (Box 55)
        - Acadian House (Joseph Clay) (Box 55)
        - Old State House or Whitfield House (Box 55)
    - Gyusiwa (Box 55)
    - Hackensack, NJ (Box 55)
    - Haddam, CT (Box 55)
    - Hadley, MA (Box 55)
    - Hamden, CT (Box 55)
    - Hamilton, NY (Box 55)
    - Hampton, MD (Box 55)
    - Hampstead, NC (Box 55)
    - Hampton, NH (Box 55)
    - Hancock's Bridges (Box 55)
    - Hanover, NH (Box 55)
    - Harrisburg, PA (Box 55)
      - Government Building (Box 55)
        - Dauphin County Court House (Box 55)
        - State Capitol (Box 55)
      - Stations (Box 55)
    - Hartford, CT (Box 55)
      - General (Box 55)
      - Churches (Box 55)
        - Christ Church (Box 56)
        - Roman Catholic Church (Box 56)
        - South Congregational Church (Box 56)
      - Plans/Planning (Box 56)
      - Government Buildings (Box 56)
        - Court Building (Box 56)
        - State House (Box 56)
        - Old State House (Box 56)
        - State Capitol (Box 56)
          - Competition Drawings (Box 56)
          - State Capitol as built (Box 56)
      - Houses & Residences (Box 56)
        - Various (Box 56)
        - Arms Mear (Box 56)
        - Olmstead House (Box 56)
        - Sigourney House (Box 56)
        - Mark Twain House (Box 56)
      - Museums (Box 56)
        - Wadsworth Athenaeum (Box 56)
      - Office Buildings (Box 56)
        - CT. General Life Insurance Company (Box 56)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 56)
      - Schools (Box 56)
        - Trinity College (Box 56)
      - Squares (Box 56)
    - Harvey Cedars, NY (Box 57)
    - Harwinton, CT (Box 57)
    - Haverhill, MA (Box 57)
    - Haverhill, NH (Box 57)
    - Haystack Mt., ME (Box 57)
    - Hewlett Harbor, L.I., NY (Box 57)
    - Hicksville, NY (Box 57)
    - Highland Park, IL (Box 57)
      - Various (Box 57)
      - Ward Willets House (Box 57)
    - Hillsborough, CA (Box 57)
      - Robbins House (Box 57)
      - Hilton, VA (Box 57)
    - Hingham, MA (Box 57)
    - Hoboken, NJ (Box 57)
    - Hockessin, DE (Box 57)
    - Holdridge, MN (Box 57)
    - Holland, MI (Box 57)
    - Holly Springs, MO (Box 57)
    - Hollywood, CA (Box 57)
      - Clubs (Box 57)
      - Houses (Box 57)
      - Office Buildings (Box 57)
        - C.B.S. Studios (Box 57)
      - Theaters (Box 57)
    - Holyoke, MA (Box 57)
    - Honesdale, PA (Box 58)
    - Honolulu, HI (Box 58)
    - Horsham, PA (Box 58)
    - Houston, TX (Box 58)
      - Various (Box 58)
      - Museums (Box 58)
        - Museum of Fine Arts (Box 58)
      - Schools (Box 58)
        - Rice Institute (Box 58)
        - University of Saint Thomas (Box 58)
    - Hudson, NY (Box 58)
    - Hyde Park, NY (Box 58)
    - Huntington, L.I., NY (Box 58)
    - Imperial Valley, CA (Box 58)
    - Indianapolis, IN (Box 58)
    - Ipswich, MA (Box 58)
      - Houses (Box 58)
        - Dodge House (Box 58)
        - Whipple House (Box 58)
    - Irvington, IN (Box 58)
    - Irvington, NY (Box 58)
    - Isleta, NM (Box 59)
    - Islip, NY (Box 59)
    - Istaca, MN (Box 59)
    - Ithaca, NY (Box 59)
      - Houses (Box 59)
      - Schools (Box 59)
        - Cornell University (Box 59)
          - Baker Hall (Box 59)
          - Baker Tower (Box 59)
          - Schoeilkof Field Stadium (Box 59)
    - Jackson, MS (Box 59)
    - Jackson Hall, WY (Box 59)
    - Jacksonville, FL (Box 59)
    - Jamaica Plain, MA (Box 59)
    - Jamestown, RI (Box 59)
    - Jefferson City, MO (Box 59)
    - Jeffersonville, OH (Box 59)
    - Jenkintown, PA (Box 59)
    - Jersey City (Box 59)
    - Joliet, IL (Box 59)
    - Jones Beach, L.I., NY (Box 59)
    - Joppa, MD (Box 59)
    - Jonesboro, AR (Box 59)
    - Kalamazoo, MI (Box 59)
    - Kankakee, IL (Box 59)
      - Houses (Box 59)
        - Bradley House (Box 59)
        - Hickox House (Box 59)
      - Industrial Building (Box 59)
    - Kansas City, MO (Box 59)
      - General (Box 59)
      - Church (Box 59)
        - Community Church (Box 59)
      - Houses (Box 59)
      - Museums (Box 60)
      - Office Buildings (Box 60)
      - Stores (Box 60)
    - Keene, NH (Box 60)
    - Kenilworth, IL (Box 60)
    - Kennebunkport, ME (Box 60)
      - Houses (Box 60)
    - Kensington, IL (Box 60)
    - Kent, CT (Box 60)
    - Kent Woodlands, CA (Box 60)
      - MaCoy Houses (Box 60)
    - Kingston, RI (Box 60)
    - Kingsport, TN (Box 60)
    - Kirwood, MO (Box 60)
    - Kittery, ME (Box 60)
    - Knoxville, TN (Box 60)
    - Lafayette, CA (Box 60)
    - Laguna, NM (Box 60)
    - La Jolla, CA (Box 60)
      - Clubs (Box 60)
      - Houses (Box 61)
      - Houses & Apartments (Box 61)
      - Schools (Box 61)
    - Lake Bluff, IL (Box 61)
    - Lake Delavan, WI (Box 61)
    - Lake Forest, IL (Box 61)
      - Various (Box 61)
      - Houses (Box 61)
        - Longfield (Box 61)
        - McCormick House (Box 61)
      - Squares (Box 61)
    - Lake Geneva, WI (Box 61)
    - Lake George, NY (Box 61)
    - Lake Placid, NY (Box 61)
    - Lakeland, FL (Box 61)
      - Schools (Box 61)
        - Florida Southern College (Box 61)
    - Lakeville, CT (Box 61)
    - Lambertsville, NJ (Box 61)
    - Lancaster, MA (Box 61)
    - Lancaster, PA (Box 62)
    - Lancaster, SC (Box 62)
    - Lansdown, PA (Box 62)
    - Laramie, WY (Box 62)
    - Larchmont, NY (Box 62)
    - Las Crucas, NM (Box 62)
    - Laverock, PA (Box 62)
    - Lawrence, Long Island, NY (Box 62)
      - Houses (Box 62)
        - Geller House (Box 62)
        - Sunset Hall (Box 62)
    - Lebanon, CT (Box 62)
      - Churches (Box 62)
      - Houses (Box 62)
    - Leesburg, OH (Box 62)
    - Lenox, MA (Box 62)
      - Government Buildings (Box 62)
      - Houses (Box 62)
        - Belle Fontaine (Box 62)
        - The Homestead (Box 62)
    - Levittown, PA (Box 62)
    - Lexington, KY (Box 63)
    - Lexington, MA (Box 63)
    - Lexington, VA (Box 63)
    - Liberty, MO (Box 63)
    - Liberty town, MD (Box 63)
    - Libertyville, IL (Box 63)
    - Limestone, ME (Box 63)
    - Lincoln, MA (Box 63)
      - Houses (Box 63)
        - Bogner House (Box 63)
        - Brever House (Box 63)
        - Ford House (Box 63)
        - Gropius House (Box 63)
        - Monk's House (Box 63)
        - Perkins House (Box 63)
        - Pertzoff House (Box 63)
    - Lincoln, NE (Box 63)
    - Lincoln, RI (Box 64)
    - Linda Vista, CA (Box 64)
    - Linwood, PA (Box 64)
    - Litchfield, CT (Box 64)
      - General (Box 64)
      - Churches (Box 64)
        - Congregational Church (Box 64)
        - S. Michael's (Box 64)
      - Houses (Box 64)
        - Various (Box 64)
        - Abbey House (Box 64)
        - Butler House (Box 64)
        - Deming House (Box 64)
        - Fisher House (Box 64)
        - Lynde Lord House (Box 64)
        - Seymour House (Box 64)
        - Sheldon House (Box 64)
          Xx Fisher House
        - Tallmadge House (Box 64)
        - Tapping Reeve House (Box 64)
        - Wadsworth House (Box 64)
        - Wolcott House (Box 64)
      - Stores (Box 64)
        - Ye Old Curiosity Shop (Box 64)
    - Little Rock, AR (Box 64)
      - Government Buildings (Box 64)
      - Hotels (Box 64)
    - Llewellyn Park, NJ (Box 64)
      - Houses (Box 65)
        - Haskell House (Box 65)
        - Howard House (Box 65)
        - Nichols House (Box 65)
    - Long Haven, PA (Box 65)
    - Locust Valley, L.I., NY (Box 65)
    - Long Beach, CA (Box 65)
    - Long Branch, NJ (Box 65)
      Xx Elberon, NJ
    - Logan, UT (Box 65)
    - Long Island, NY (Box 65)
    - Long Island City, NY (Box 65)
    - Longmeadow, MA (Box 65)
    - Longview, TX (Box 65)
    - Los Angeles, CA (Box 65)
      - General (Box 65)
      - General & Planning (Box 65)
      - Houses & Apartments (Box 65)
        - Various (Box 65)
        - Dinsmuir Flats (Box 65)
        - Land Fair Apartments (Box 65)
      - Houses & Residences (Box 65)
        - Various (Box 65)
        - Barnsdall House (Box 65)
          - Exterior (Box 65)
          - Interior (Box 66)
        - Birtcher House (Box 66)
        - Urcel Daniel's House (Box 66)
        - Walter Dodge House (Box 66)
        - Ennis House (Box 66)
        - Fitzpatrick House (Box 66)
        - Freeman House (Box 66)
        - Gold House (Box 66)
        - Goodwin House (Box 66)
        - R. Johnson House (Box 66)
        - Katz House (Box 66)
        - Koblick House (Box 66)
        - Laughlin House (Box 66)
        - Lovell House (Box 66)
        - Musk House (Box 66)
        - Neutra House pre-1942 (Box 66)
        - Martha Raye House (Box 66)
        - Research House (Box 66)
        - Rose House (Box 66)
        - Schindler House (Box 66)
        - Storer House (Box 66)
        - Strauss House (Box 66)
        - Sturges House (Box 66)
        - Walker House (Box 66)
        - Wilson House (Box 66)
      - Housing (Box 66)
        - Advanced Development Company (Box 66)
        - Baldwin Hills Village (Box 66)
        - Channel Heights (Box 66)
          Xx San Pedro, CA
        - Sunset Tower Apartments (Box 66)
        - Wyverwood Village (Box 66)
      - Libraries (Box 66)
        - Belvedere Gardens Library (Box 66)
        - Public Library (Box 67)
      - Office Buildings (Box 67)
        - Various (Box 67)
        - Bradbury Building (Box 67)
        - Matson Line Ticket Office (Box 67)
        - Petroleum Building (Box 67)
        - Richfield Building (Box 67)
        - Schindler Office (Box 67)
        - Western Airlines Office (Box 67)
      - Schools (Box 67)
        - Emerson Junior High School (Box 67)
        - Aline Barnsdall Kindergarten (Box 67)
      - Stores (Box 67)
        - Sears Roebuck (Box 67)
      - Theaters (Box 67)
        - Mayan Theater (Box 67)
    - Louisiana, State of (Box 67)
      - Belle Grove (Box 67)
      - Ascension Parish (Box 67)
        - Belle Helene (Ashland) (Box 67)
        - Hermitage (Box 67)
        - Houmas House (Burnside) (Box 67)
      - Baton Rouge Parish (East & West) (Box 67)
      - S. James Parish (Box 67)
        - Oak Alley (Box 67)
    - Louisville, KY (Box 67)
    - Lowder, IL (Box 67)
    - Lowell, MA (Box 67)
    - Lowndes Grove, SC (Box 68)
    - Lynchburg, VA (Box 68)
    - Lynn, MA (Box 68)
    - Macon, GA (Box 68)
    - Madison, CT (Box 68)
    - Madison, IN (Box 68)
    - Madison, NJ (Box 68)
    - Madison, WI (Box 68)
      - Churches (Box 68)
      - Government Buildings (Box 68)
        - City Hall (Box 68)
        - State Capitol (Box 68)
      - Houses (Box 68)
        - Bradley House (Box 68)
        - Jacobs House I, 1937 (Box 68)
        - J.C. Pew House (Box 68)
      - Housing (Box 68)
      - Industrial Building (Box 68)
      - Recreation (Box 68)
    - Malden, MA (Box 68)
    - Mamaroneck, NY (Box 68)
      - Houses (Box 68)
        - Osborn House (Box 68)
    - Manchester, CT (Box 68)
    - Manchester by the Sea, MA (Box 68)
      - Houses (Box 68)
    - Manchester, PA (Box 68)
    - Manhasset, NY (Box 68)
    - Manheim, PA (Box 68)
    - Maplewood, NJ (Box 69)
    - Marblehead, MA (Box 69)
      - Jeremiah Lee (Box 69)
    - Marinette, WI (Box 69)
    - Martha's Vineyard, MA (Box 69)
      Xx for houses in specific towns, see under the name
    - Maryland, State of (Box 69)
      - Various (Box 69)
      - Anne Arundel County (Box 69)
        - Tulip Hill (Box 69)
        - Whitehall (Box 69)
      - Calvert County (Box 69)
      - Cecil County (Box 69)
        - Bohemia (Box 69)
      - Kent County (Box 69)
      - Prince George County (Box 69)
      - Somerset County (Box 69)
      - Talbot County (Box 69)
        - Wye House (Box 69)
    - Maryville, TN (Box 69)
    - Mason City, IA (Box 69)
      - Hotels (Box 69)
      - Houses (Box 69)
        - Blythe House (Box 69)
        - Melson House (Box 69)
        - Page House (Box 69)
    - Mattapan, MA (Box 69)
    - Mayville, NY (Box 69)
    - Maywood, IL (Box 69)
    - McCloud River, CA (Box 69)
    - Meadville, PA (Box 69)
    - Medford, MA (Box 69)
      - Houses (Box 69)
        - Various (Box 69)
        - Blanchard House (Box 69)
        - Royal or Usher House (Box 69)
        - Tufts on Craddock House (Box 69)
    - Melrose Park, PA (Box 70)
    - Memphis, TN (Box 70)
    - Meriden, CT (Box 70)
    - Miami, FL (Box 70)
    - Middlebury, VT (Box 70)
    - Middlebury, WI (Box 70)
      - Jacobs House II, 1948 (Box 70)
    - Middlebury, CT (Box 70)
      - General (Box 70)
      - Government Buildings (Box 70)
      - Houses (Box 70)
        - Alsop House (Box 70)
        - S. Russell House (Box 70)
    - Middletown, NY (Box 70)
    - Midland, MI (Box 70)
      - Clubs (Box 70)
        - Midland Country Club (Box 70)
      - Houses (Box 70)
        - Cavanag House (Box 70)
        - A.B. Dow House (Box 70)
        - Earl Stein House (Box 70)
        - Whitman House (Box 70)
      - Office Buildings (Box 70)
    - Milford, CT (Box 70)
      - General (Box 70)
      - Churches (Box 70)
      - Houses (Box 70)
    - Milford, PA (Box 70)
    - Milledgeville, GA (Box 70)
    - Mill Valley, CA (Box 70)
    - Milton, MA (Box 70)
      - Houses (Box 70)
    - Milton, WI (Box 70)
    - Milwaukee, WI (Box 71)
      - Various (Box 71)
      - South Police Station St. (Box 71)
      - Houses (Box 71)
    - Minneapolis, MN (Box 71)
      - Various (Box 71)
      - Churches (Box 71)
        - Lakewood Cemetery Church (Box 71)
        - S. Francis Cabrini (Box 71)